NEVER SEEN BEFORE: T.B. Joshua's Early Ministry!!!
After conducting the Sunday service, Prophet T.B. Joshua would usually join the members to the cantine.
He serves water to the members.
NEVER SEEN BEFORE: T.B. Joshua's Early Ministry!!!
He stands in line to buy his food.
Ma, let me pay for the food you are buying.
Will this food be enough for you?
Yes.
I would like to buy some yam.
Three naira yam.
This will not be enough for me.
Give me five naira yam.
What do you want to buy?
Five naira beans and five naira yam.
Give the food to him. This is the money. I will come back to collect my change.
NEVER SEEN BEFORE: T.B. Joshua's Early Ministry!!!
Occasionally, Prophet T.B. Joshua would travel by public truck.
As busy as he was, Prophet T.B. Joshua regularly took time out of his busy schedule
to join the workers preparing food in the kitchen.
NEVER SEEN BEFORE: T.B. Joshua's Early Ministry!!!
This is one of the services at the first building at the new site of The SCOAN.
In fulfillment of the prophecy given by the man of God at the prayer mountain,
here, you could see hundreds of people from around the world who have come
to listen to the Word of God that Jesus Christ has revealed to his servant Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Spending Time With Children
Prophet T.B. Joshua takes time out during the service
to visit the children in the Sunday School department.
The children, overjoyed to see their pastor, greet him with hugs and laughter.
Look at the joy on T.B. Joshua's face as he greets the children.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Spending Time With Children
Time with Jesus is time with joy
Celebrating with the children of The SCOAN, T.B. Joshua spends his time
playing and relating with them during the Sunday service.
Truly in the presence of God, there is fullness of joy.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Spending Time With Children
Damage Done To The Church By Heavy Rain
During the rainy season, heavy rainstorms continued to flood the entire church premises.
This is Prophet T.B. Joshua in the rain, in a dark-coloured jacket.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Surveying Damage Done To The Church By Heavy Rain
Prophet T.B. Joshua Rebuilding A Wall In The Church Damaged By The Storm
Prophet T.B. Joshua works alongside the members to rebuild a wall
that had been destroyed by the storm.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Rebuilding A Wall In The Church Damaged By The Storm
Despite his many activities, Prophet T.B. Joshua never abandoned his mission.
He knew who he was and what he was about.
Nothing could take his mind, time and energy from preaching the Word of God every single service day.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Takes Public Transport To The Prayer Mountain After The Service
Having just finished the service, Prophet T.B. Joshua leaves the church
and boards a motorcycle to make his way to the prayer mountain.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Takes Public Transport To The Prayer Mountain After The Service
Here is Prophet T.B. Joshua surveying the church premises
after heavy rain had once again caused flooding.
3rd Church
Prophet T.B. Joshua is carrying a plank of wood to assist in rebuilding the church.
Prophet T.B. Joshua is packing sand, along with members of the church,
to repair the damage that was caused to the first church structure due to the heavy rainstorm.
3rd Church
Due to the increasing number of worshippers attending the church,
the Holy Spirit instructed Prophet T.B. Joshua to move to a new location
to accommodate the influx of new worshippers.
In 1994, the church moved to Ikotun Egbe, Lagos, Nigeria.
This is the fourth building of The SCOAN.
The first building at the new site.
The New Site of The Synagogue, Church Of All Nations, 1994
Amen
Thank You, Jesus!
4th Church
Inside the church are thousands of people, joyfully receiving the Word of God.
After the service, the man of God returns by motorcycle to his personal place of sanctuary -
his own prayer mountain, located 15 minutes from the church.
Here is Prophet T.B. Joshua at the age of 32.
He was the overseer of The SCOAN,
while at the same time cleaning the toilets of the church every day for three years.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Cleaning The Toilets In The Church
One may ask the question: Why did Prophet T.B. Joshua keep such a detailed record
right from the beginning of the life he lived?
He is a man of vision and his vision was inspired by the Holy Spirit.
It has God behind it, for its accomplishment.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Cleaning The Gutters In The Church
Every day for three years, Prophet T.B. Joshua also cleaned the sewers of The SCOAN by hand.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Cleaning The Benches And Fans In The Church
Hundreds of benches and fans were installed inside the new church
for the thousands of members that came daily to attend the services.
Not only did Prophet T.B. Joshua minister to the congregation,
he also gladly and faithfully cleaned the fans and benches daily.
There were hundreds of them.
He cleaned them all.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Cleaning The Benches And Fans In The Church
As Colossians 3: 23-24 says, "Whatever you do, work at it with all your heart,
as working for the Lord, not for men, since you know you will receive an inheritance
from the Lord as a reward. It is the Lord Christ you are serving".
Prophet T.B. Joshua Cleaning The Benches And Fans In The Church
Prophet T.B. Joshua Scrubbing The Floor Of The Church
He is seen here, cleaning the floor of an entrance to the church.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Eating With Children
As is his practice, T.B. Joshua regularly takes time out to share food with the children
and enjoy their presence.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Eating With A Child
Prophet T.B. Joshua Spending Time With Children
Occasionally, T.B. Joshua can be found sitting among the children in their Sunday School class
and visiting the babies in the Nursing Mothers section of the church.
He is an integral part of every department of the church.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Spending Time With Children
Prophet T.B. Joshua Travelling To The Church By Public Transport
Prophet T.B. Joshua is returning from a quiet moment of devotion in prayer at the prayer mountain
to resume his activities at the church.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Travelling To The Church By Public Transport
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.